Yeah.
Let's do things differently, this time.
Like, so differently.
His name is Miles Morales.
He was bitten by a radioactive spider.
And he's not the only one.
He hasn't always had it easy.
And now he's on his own.
And he's not the only one.
You think you know the rest?
You don't.
You've been a lot under the rest, but...
I didn't...
I didn't want to hurt him.
But I did.
This song over?
It seems over.
Are you okay?
You don't hang out and
you don't want to talk.
I didn't join a band so I
could talk about my feelings.
Well, I did.
I joined it so I could hit
my feelings with sticks.
If you don't tell someone what's
going on, you're gonna survive.
I'm fine.
That's not how someone
who's fine would say that.
I'm great.
Thanks.
How are you?
I'm great.
Thanks.
How are you?
Fine.
When?
Come on.
I don't get you.
You're right.
I played drums.
I always wanted to be in a band.
Guess I just never found the right one.
In this line of work, you
always wind up a solo act.
Before Miles, there was Peter.
Is this that dangerous menace?
Oh, no, no.
She seems like a good guy.
Why wear a mask if you got nothing to hide.
All right, no politics at the dinner.
Thank you, May.
But they didn't really know me.
And I didn't really know him either.
that was too late.
No, no, no, no, no, what did you tell her?
I just... wanted to be special.
Like you.
When?
Don't worry.
Just go ahead.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Don't.
There it is.
Don't go.
I never really made
another friend after that.
Except one.
But he's not here.
And there's no way to get there.
I've done made a bit harder.
Peter Parker hated my table.
He was my daughter's best friend.
And I will not rest till
I find this spider wolf.
Oh, hey.
How's the van?
Uh, yeah, great.
I quit.
So, you know, thumbs up.
We, uh, we caught a break
in the spider woman case.
That's good.
We're close.
I'm telling you, I can feel it.
He too.
It'll be good for us.
Don't be so sure.
She killed your friend.
You don't know that.
What do you mean I don't know?
I do know that.
I was there.
She ran from the scene.
She didn't have a choice.
I got a job to do when.
It won't bring him back.
I don't want to argue about this, OK?
Yeah, I can tell.
Say, uh,
through punk rock to give your old man up.
Oh, this could be it.
So I'll see you later.
I'll go.
Love you.
Here, explain to me
how a guy with a 40-foot
wingspan just walks into
the room and I'm a notice.
Hey, it's New York.
Everyone's got their thing.
I'm an Irish cop.
Maybe you love pasta or something.
Everybody on my signal.
Look at who signs a spider woman.
Hey!
Yeah, we got our sign.
Puss them in on me going.
You're gonna be in there.
Good to know.
Culture!
Screaming their name usually works.
I guess that worked.
I am the Folcher, the
pinnacle of man's genius.
You're not my Folcher, but
you've made of parchment.
What kind of set world
have you brought me to?
Glitching, huh?
I'm nervous.
Where are you from, bud?
I am an artist.
I'm a judge here.
Oh, great.
We're going to stop the man.
Ooh, look at that.
You were having an espresso and some
old climbing Leonardo da Vinci da Mendon.
It's suddenly a portal up and
up and you're lined up now.
Ah.
Am I one?
Yes, it's pretty budget.
Oh, that's cool Oh, look it's your cousin
That was a good answer.
I'm sorry, who exactly
are you supposed to be?
You're the blue panther.
No.
The cape to blue satyr?
No, I'm... Dark Garfield.
No, stop.
Much Oli Bray.
I'm from another dimension.
You are?
Wow!
Actually, I'm not confused.
My name is Miguel O'Hare.
I need an elite strike force dedicated
to the security of the multiples.
I just forget it.
Can you go to any dimension
you want with that watch today?
It's much cooler than a watch.
Okay, sensitive.
Look, there is a big flying
church from the Renaissance.
I have to bring the
justice, so if you don't mind.
It's all right.
I'll take it from here.
OK, knock yourself up.
What are you saying like that?
I don't know.
You really want to hang up
your shotgun mess, by the way.
What next?
Team pins collide.
Or are you guys talking about?
None of your business.
You shut up.
Kelsey.
Yeah.
This is the multi-bird.
You left a whole wide
enough for guys like him.
For granted, we get shot
into the wrong dimension.
I'm stuck putting everybody back where they
belong for all the time as space collapses.
They're going to get me started on Dr.
Strange, a little nerd
back on Earth's 1999.
This Dr.
Strange, sounds like he made
you shouldn't practice medicine.
So you want me to handle this warrant or...
Huh, okay.
Lilac, can you please?
You know?
Nah, you gotta say it first.
Go for backup.
What?
Call for backup.
Come on.
Please just call for...
Yeah, I already called her.
Yeah!
What are you gonna do with that?
Spider-women.
Me too.
Are you, uh... Oh, this?
We don't know the sex yet.
My husband wants it to be a surprise.
He's really corny.
But so hot.
Will you adopt me?
What?
Guys, can we help you with the
fire bringing direct time to space?
No.
We can use the help.
Is it cause she called you dark Garfield?
No.
Do you say anything but now?
Yes.
Why not?
You know what?
Enough of this.
Take a good look at him.
I'm gonna head back.
Come on!
You don't look like a good guy
Yeah, I think it's a Banksy
That's what I was gonna do
Hands in the air.
Captain, come on.
Suspect is armed.
With what?
I'm out of words.
Get down on the ground.
Which is it?
Hands in the air.
Get down on the ground.
You're under arrest.
I just saved a bunch of people.
The martyr of Peter Park.
Captain, come on.
Right to remain silent.
You don't understand.
Dad I've I've thought about telling
you but you can see why I didn't
want to you can see why I didn't
want to tell you I Didn't harder Peter.
I didn't I didn't know it was him.
I didn't have a home
have you been lying to me?
Can you just, can you
just not be a cop for
a second and be my
dad here and listen to me?
Do you really think I'm a murderer?
You're in this to help people, right?
Right?
So am I.
And the way to help
right now is to listen to me.
Please, dad, you're all I have left.
You have the right to remain silent.
What?
Anything you say can and
what are you going to do?
Really?
This is afraid of me?
You have the right to return.
Don't get anything.
Just breathe.
We got you.
Right, Miguel?
Lila, I was going this mess.
No further anomaly can remain as intact.
Yeah.
Well, join the club.
I know he's just a sophomore, but we want
to get a jump on the college conversation.
So I'm sure he's going
to be here any minute.
He's very serious about his future.
Excuse me, do you have an ATM machine?
Yeah, we're on here in the box.
Preferably not changed to the wall.
Nothing.
This should be simple enough.
Just make a hole.
Grab the money.
Nope, that's not right.
Just get me your money.
Yo, what you doing back here, man?
Nothing.
Everything is everything's cool, man.
Oh, good.
Just forgot my pinned up.
I'm going to do this.
I've never rubbed anybody in my life.
Please don't make this
a bad experience for me.
If he gave for himself.
Oh, wow, this is a great powder.
I'm a scientist.
I am.
I used to work there.
I was actually considered
handsome by scientists.
I'm so sorry.
First of all, I'm not even robbing you.
I mean, this H.M.
machine doesn't even belong to you, right?
This belongs to the bank.
They're the real criminals.
I can't really get a job
anywhere anymore being
like this, so I've turned
to the life of crime.
Why don't people say ATM machine?
Who said that?
The M stands for machines.
Spider!
I'm gonna show you
for this beef patty, man.
Spidey, if you catch him,
send the old spreader.
Oh, Spiderman.
Wow.
This is real.
So are you like a cow or a Dalmatian?
I am.
This is spot.
We meet again, Spiderman.
Oh, that's funny.
Of course not.
So is that a costume?
Unfortunately, for
both of us, this is skin.
Oh, hey.
You see, I'm from your past.
One year ago.
Hold up.
Oh, come on.
Uh-oh.
Well, this has been some time.
Who are you talking to?
But I really got to wrap this up.
This is going to be a while.
It's like, hey.
Hey.
Hey
My name is Miles Morales.
I was bitten by a radioactive spider.
And for the last year and four months, I've
been Brooklyn's one and only Spider-Man.
And things are going great.
You can hurt somebody.
Captain All sorts of bad guys.
This act like a regular super
villain, so I can catch you.
I designed my new soup, with
some fly ambiance down the side.
Aunt May moved to Florida.
I guess, off the Jeopardy,
endorsed baby powder.
Apologize for endorsing baby powder.
Made a mistake.
My mustache came in, wash, and out.
I made another mistake.
I didn't develop any new
tools from my venom thing.
How much longer can I keep
lying about who I really am?
I hear that in the
Spider-Man's Puerto Rican.
He seems more Dominican to me.
I mean, would they get it if I told them?
We love you, except you, even
though you haven't lied to us for a year.
Maybe in some other universe.
Sometimes I just wish
I was at the only one.
I don't dwell on them.
I miss my uncle sometimes.
My uncle seems like what you do.
Even though he turned
out to be the problem.
I'm trying to do what he told me.
Just keep going.
You're looking at your text.
You're going to say
this the fight of our lives.
Sorry, just a second.
No, no, no.
Go ahead.
Take the call.
Turn off your phone at a movie theater.
You don't turn it off
when you're fighting me.
Oh, and a minute.
Hey, what did all this one word?
That's cute, right?
The youth.
That's weird.
There's the bubbles now.
Hold on.
I don't think I want this costume anymore.
I'm Spiderman.
No one can take that away from him.
I can't help it if we're the same size
Every person is a universe
and my job is to capture
your person's universe
on this piece of paper.
That's blank.
Exactly.
I have no idea who this kid is.
I don't know if he knows.
And he's got to decide if
he's going to commit himself to
his future or whatever he's
doing instead of being here.
Can't have your cake and eat it to him.
Unless you bake two cakes.
I know.
Look, I gotta get back
to being a great student.
So give him right this quick.
Okay.
Miles is great.
They're pretty good.
A-N-A-P physics.
That's my little man.
And AP Studio art.
He takes after his uncle.
A-minus in English.
She's a tough grader.
And a B-in Spanish.
Whoo!
Okay.
My-Are you trying to make
me tell you what to say?
I'm not there, Mommy.
That's so no, that's my fault.
Okay, guys.
I don't know my fault.
I don't know my class in Spanish.
Oh, I just missed a few classes.
Oh, just a few classes.
Well, what's a few?
I mean, you know, like...
Five!
Actually, Zach.
Good.
Oh.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
What takes after his uncle?
I just have a lot going on.
All right.
We can still salvage this.
I'm sorry.
Salvage.
Miles has a great story to tell.
I mean, a story at all seems grumpy.
Your name is Miles Morales.
Correct.
You grew up in a
struggling immigrant family.
I'm from Puerto Rico.
Puerto Rico is part of America.
We on a floor in Brooklyn.
I'm struggling.
It doesn't matter.
You're all struggling.
I'll make up the next week.
And now, his dream is to attend
the top physics program in the nation.
Whatever it takes, we'll
do it at Princeton University.
A New Jersey?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Let's do far.
New Jersey's too far from New York.
His great school is in Brooklyn.
Mama.
Preston has the best quantum
researchers in the country.
They're moving electrons
across dimensional thresholds.
I mean, they're studying dark matter.
Yeah, I don't know.
I could help figure out how
to travel to other dimensions.
Yeah, okay.
Oh, yeah, that sounds
like a really good fake job.
Dad, when you were my age,
you followed your dream and went
out on your own to start a
business with Uncle Anne, right?
That's different.
We used to see when you were born.
What's your mom used to look?
Life is a journey.
You all got me into this school because
you thought I could do something special.
And now I think so too.
And the special thing I want to do is this.
There are people out there who can literally
teach me the things I want to learn.
But they aren't all in Brooklyn.
That's your story.
Now, just stick to mine.
You're killing me.
Oh, I gotta go.
You guys just keep talking.
This is all right.
Wait.
Did you order the cake for tonight?
Totally.
I'm, you know, call me.
I gotta go.
All right.
Bye.
This kid.
I swear, what are we gonna do with that?
I gotta go.
What?
You're gonna leave.
You leave.
You never believe.
Why am I here?
I know.
I'm so sorry, but we'll figure it out.
Together.
Wow.
Excuse me.
I'm so sorry.
He's lying to you.
Jeff, your son.
He's lying.
And I think you know it.
How's your essay?
I'm marinating.
This is part of my process.
Oh, oh, really?
I think your guy got away.
Thanks, I'm on it.
Yeah, you seem really stressed.
I agree.
You're stretched too thin.
All right, thanks for the tip.
That was bad.
I know.
What's a really part of it with this kid?
I don't know.
No, Harry.
Spiderman.
Officer Verale.
I mean, oh, he's so marvelous.
Does not want to look like you.
Hey, hey!
You can't go here, man!
This is funny.
Oh, my lady's here!
You know how many women more?
I got raped for that!
You left in the middle
of a fight, but you're not.
It was a story!
What's inconsiderate and
super rude and a little cocker.
Yeah, you got me a real.
What's the bag?
I'm right now.
And, kind.
He's barely a villain of the witch.
What you call me?
Realize him right here, man.
That's a mess!
That's not enough to throw it.
Of course we end up back here.
I am.
That's so silly.
Imagine that.
Is it all coming back to you
talking about the creation events?
What?
Yeah.
Hey, we got cut off.
Stop.
Destiny brought us here.
You see now, don't you?
I really don't.
I am your nemesis.
You are not you, Miss.
You can't contain us.
You really don't remember
what you did to me?
What I did for you?
Uh, no.
I worked at Aquamax.
I ran a test on this collider that brought
a spider here from another dimension.
42.
It's home dimension.
It escaped, and it bit you.
My spider made you Spider-Man.
What?
You ran through the cafeteria.
You hit me with a bagel.
I did a lot of different villains
with a lot of different fool.
Make your flippy little sassy jokes.
Everyone loves them.
But no one knows what it feels
like to be on the other side of them.
I'm just trying to lighten the moon.
I created you.
You created me.
Spider-Man, what is the weirdest that guy?
I didn't.
He's talking crazy.
I was in this collider
room when you blow it up.
Because of you, I lost my jobs, my life,
my face, my family won't even look at me.
I made you do a hero.
You made me this.
Look at me!
You missed me!
I'll make you miss me, baby!
Ow!
I am your antenna!
Where'd he go?
He kicked his own butt.
You know we're supposed
to catch the bad guys, right?
I always do.
Gutierrez get the crane man I am trying
to do right out I mean I'm trying you need
to be a better role model great role model
Hey Gutierrez you can cancel the crane
Do you want to talk about it?
Are you crazy?
Well, many of your generation
ignored their mental health, too.
What am I?
What am I even doing?
Because no matter what I do,
someone always think something with it.
I know the villain.
Oh, yes, son.
How's he doing?
You think he's going to figure it all out?
Honestly?
Yeah.
He's a good kid.
Yeah?
You know it's scary.
He says these things that are so smart.
Cool.
Well, I should probably-He does
these things that are so stupid.
I just don't want him to mess it up.
Maybe get off the kids ass.
I'm sorry.
What?
I don't know.
And I hate that he's not
being honest with me.
Maybe he's scared to talk to you.
Hi.
Would anyone be scared to talk to me?
I died.
I don't know.
I think you're getting pretty
good at being a parent.
You think you got it lit.
And then they go and grow up.
I just don't want to lose them, you know?
Well, as an objective
observer with no skin in the
game, I say, you got to let
him spread his wings, man.
Like this.
Yeah.
This is a nice what is.
I should go.
Yeah, and catch that holes guy.
Don't worry.
I don't think that guy's
going to show his face again.
What?
Okay.
I think I kicked myself into myself.
Well, this is new.
Hello.
Hello, Echo, Echo, Echo, Echo.
Hypothesis.
I'm going to put my head in that hole.
Oh, no.
That was... cool.
My holes can take me anywhere.
Excuse me.
Hi.
Sorry to bug you.
I know you're busy, sorry.
What are you?
I know it's weird.
I just came out of nowhere, but I think I'm
becoming a trans-dimensional super being.
So?
So.
I'm literally splitting the
fabric of space and time.
For you, it's just a Tuesday night.
You're acting like weird stuff like
this happens to you all the time.
Can I have some gum?
The power of the multiverse
and the palm of my hand.
My holes aren't a curse.
They're the answer.
Can you stop talking about your holes?
You're making everyone
uncomfortable over you.
No, no, no, no, no.
You're going to love this.
Look, look, look.
I'm out of spots, wouldn't you?
Know what?
Uh, as you were, gentlemen,
I'm coming for you, Spider-Man.
Uh, no.
Good morning, Spider-Man.
Page one for the decent
picture of the story.
You're absolutely right, boss.
I'm sick.
Shut up.
Uh-huh.
Get on it.
I got a boss.
All right.
I'm on it.
Yeah.
I need a raise.
Big, big.
Big Elf, it's Peter.
We got an anomaly.
Thank you, Peter.
You're one of our best.
Jess, who's on this?
Big, big.
Are you seeing my eyes?
No?
What are you seeing my eyes?
Are you seeing my eyes?
And I want you to know,
no matter what, even though
we've had our ups and downs,
I am so proud of you today.
And every day, parentheses, mostly, LOL.
Hey, missus.
It won't fit on one cake.
Can't you write smaller?
Can't you write shorter?
What else can I say about Jeff?
that he was almost ten pounds as a baby.
I know.
I know you're gonna be embarrassed.
I mean, I was killed in mother.
Look at those shoulders.
Oh, no.
Okay.
That's okay.
I think the mic number makes for you.
Okay.
Thank you, Rio, for that.
You did always know
what I wanted to do in life.
I was pulled in a lot of different
directions when I was young.
You know me and my brother
came up in his neighborhood
just a couple of knuckleheads
running the streets.
You guys used to chase
us out of your stores and now
you can believe it is
much after look out for you.
And then I had a kid and
everything changed for the better.
And I don't even know about getting a
toast cuz I asked you to talk to you all.
So to my brother, who
we miss every single day,
is definitely up there
laughing at me right now.
They're making me cap them bro.
To my wife, me I'm old.
I can't even start because I'll never stop.
I'll take my feet.
And to my son.
The reason that I do in
the end is in the first place.
Oh, I love you, Mom.
And I will always, always be here for you.
Benny, man, come on.
Drop the beat.
I don't know where I am.
I've just been here the whole time.
Oh, yeah.
Hi, you supposed to be a vibe.
I know.
I know, but I think you're dead.
Yep.
Missy's beautiful toast.
Come on.
Did you even see the cakes?
There's some heartfelt messages on them.
That's not what I meant.
Your dad studied for eight months.
Nine.
It was like, give a birth.
No, it was.
Of course not.
You made a sin that office and
talked about that later without any job.
Give us an emergency.
Whatever.
Feed emergency.
A party with some friends I've never met.
Emergency?
Explain yourself.
Sounds like Europe's
finding you pretty well.
That's funny.
Jeff, we got a funny sign.
I'm not laughing.
Oh, I like it.
I can't hardly yet a war.
Stop.
Open up, get up, get up, get up!
I don't feel going up.
This is a cool shirt.
You know, have you checked out this shirt?
Oh, yeah.
Who are you running around with anyway?
Just?
Is it Genki?
I never liked him.
Yes, you did.
It caused me by my first name.
We hate them.
I have more friends than just Genki.
Like who?
Well, there's Peter.
You know?
But he left town.
There's Gwanda, you know?
She also left town.
Miles book.
That moonbreak.
Is that spanglish?
Has it ever occurred to you
that maybe I'm just doing benign,
private, unremarkable things
when I'm not with you guys?
No, never.
I am 15 years old.
I am basically an adult.
Oh, right.
You don't even have a driver's license.
This is mine.
Because we live in New
York and never plan to leave.
It's my life.
It's not your life.
It's mine.
And your father's and your
willows, the abuelas, who
put you in this spot that
I'd give anything to be in.
All right.
Whatever.
What ever?
I don't think I can say it, please.
Something that I can say.
See it.
You're grounded.
What?
Oh, yeah.
Or how long?
I'm on.
Dad.
Mom, are you seriously?
Yeah.
Dad, serious.
You don't understand.
You're right.
You are right.
I have no idea what's going on with you.
So why don't you tell me?
Listen to me.
OK, champ, you got it.
Go for it.
Say whatever you want to say.
What do you got to tell me so bad?
You know what?
Never mind.
All right, great.
Walk away.
Because now you got two months!
That was good, right?
Two months.
And the night I'm so
sorry Get in the time
like life is on We'll
speak to the thousands
How did you get-How have you been?
Uh, I've been-Good.
I've been, yeah, just great.
Look at you.
You, uh, you grew, huh?
Had a little gross birth.
Yeah, yeah.
Your pair has gotten... Pinker?
Is this the room you grew up in?
It is, um, but my dorm
room is-it's very adult.
Cool, yeah, no, I used to play
with these when I was younger too.
Uh, this is-this is-this
is-this is collectible.
Oh, but you still have this one!
Which one?
Are these your drawings?
What?
No, they're good.
Wow, there's so many.
I missed you too.
So what are you doing here?
I mean, I thought I'd never see you again.
Want to get out of here?
I ground it.
Belmer.
Is Spider-Man grounded?
I mean...
Your dad's ready to listen now.
There's another lead to society
with all the best fighter people in it.
Okay, so there's a lady.
Jess Drew.
I'm learning so much from her.
Oh, yeah, I've learned a lot of stuff too.
I've leveled up my whole thing.
Oh, yeah?
Let's see if that goes right the needle.
Oh, he's like a ninja of vampires
Spider-Man, but a good guy?
A vampire, good guy.
A fake good mother to see that.
So how long ago did they invite you?
I was only like a few months ago.
I'm not just kind of a long time, isn't it?
Okay, this one comes with two.
Look at you.
Look at me.
So this club, look at that dumb dumb.
Kind of stuff do you do?
Kind of strange, 10 points.
We're trying to keep the
multiverse from collapsing.
But though we did that already.
Like last week we had this mission
to some Shakespeare dimensions.
And Hopey and I just
like, oh wait, who's home?
Oh my gosh, he's in love with him.
Let's be crashing his dimensions sometimes.
What does that mean?
You stay overnight or?
Anyway, listen there, they're
pretty strict about where I go, right?
I really would have come to see you sooner.
Right.
So, uh, so why'd you come now?
Don't, don't.
Yeah.
Hey, what?
You can't tell me.
Where'd you go?
Hey, hey, you on?
What are you doing?
Waiting for you.
This is a cool thinking spot, right?
I mean, who needs a treadmill when
you have the Williamsburg bank building?
So, you and your dad,
you still haven't talked?
What exactly would we talk about?
Hey dad, how the last few months been?
Still think I murdered my best friend?
Well, I mean, my parents...
I mean, maybe if I told them... Don't.
Trust me, I'm not.
Well... Maybe some things
are supposed to be just for us.
That's a nice way to think about it.
Just a really emotionally intelligent guy.
Beyond my use.
You know what really is
always so great to talk to you?
Yeah?
Yeah.
I mean, how many people
can you talk to about this stuff?
You don't even know.
What?
You're the only friend I've ever
really made after Peter died.
Other than Hobie, all right?
That's different.
Yeah?
How's that?
I don't know.
You and me, it's... We're the same.
And the important ways, you know.
In every other universe, Gwen
Stacy falls for Spider-Man.
And in every other
universe, it doesn't end well.
Well, this is the first
time for everything, right?
Wow, buildings make me hungry.
These platinum are
such a deep pride feeling.
She looks golden at her mouth.
I bet she doesn't even speak Spanish.
Well, everybody does.
This keeps you from
glitching another dimension.
Yeah, it's pretty cool.
What's it gonna take from Miguel
O'Hara to notice Miles Morales?
I'll put in a good word.
I'm just saying if I had a
watch, I could come with you.
Miles.
I did save the multiverse.
It's a really small elite strike force.
I can turn invisible.
There's just like electric power.
There aren't a lot of slots.
Ah, right.
Look, if it was up to me, you.
Oh, no, no, no, don't do that.
Miles.
All right.
It's really delicate.
Sorry.
I didn't mean to snap.
OK. All right.
I'm sorry.
Hello.
Hi.
I'm Miles.
I'm Brio.
Hi.
I've heard so much about you.
We were using my first name.
OK.
This is nice.
We found it in Miles' room, so.
I guess he must have been there.
And you must be Jack.
You got me, Jeff.
That's very sweet, Jeff.
You must me and Lieutenant
Morales soon to be Captain Morales.
Captain.
Wanda and I are friends from school.
Yeah, yeah, we were just catching up.
Don't take me from me.
I'm just kidding.
He's grounded so you can't.
Don't break his heart.
Shoot, I have to go.
Really?
Yeah, I have my, uh,
forgot to get my steps in.
Uh, really, really wish
I could stay longer.
I, I'm, I'm sorry.
Bye.
Yeah, bye.
I can hear you being quiet, Mom.
I am.
Hope I didn't ice your game, man.
No one my age says those
words in that order, Mom.
It's just hard to see my little man
not being my little boy all the time.
Yeah.
That's how you know
you can tell me anything.
No, I meant theta, center of the Sothros.
I'm
I'm sorry I was leaving.
Go.
She seems like a nice girl.
Is this a trick?
That's not a trick.
Jeez.
What are you?
Let me fix you just...
For years, I've been taking
care of this little boy, right?
Making sure he is loved, but he feels
like he belongs wherever he wants to be.
He wants to go onto the
world and do great big things.
And what I worry about most is
they won't look out for you like us.
They won't root for you like us.
So, here's the deal.
Wherever you go from here, you have to promise
to take care of that little boy for me.
Make sure he never
forgets where he came from.
And he never doubts that he's loved.
And he never lets anyone,
that those big fancy places
he's gonna be in, tell him
that he doesn't belong there.
When he comes home,
and he'd better come home.
You're going to be early, and you're
going to be holding a normal, nice kick.
Yeah, OK. You got to promise, Miles.
I promise.
Just don't get lost.
Mel, yes.
All right.
Cool.
And you see on, Mommy?
You come back.
You're still grounded.
Yeah, I'm smiling like
it's a joke, but it's true.
Yeah, I figured.
See you later with a cake.
Okay, we bounce this shape.
We roll it up.
We gotta stay straight.
Keep blowing this heart.
Now something's gonna blow with me.
I never stop.
I don't know.
Nothing can shake me.
On this, won't stand up my senses.
I won't stop for a finish.
I chew my shirt and I will visit.
On the way to go, he's gonna do this thing.
No thing can shake me now.
No thing can break me down.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No thing can shake me now.
Show me what happened.
I need more spots!
Oh my god, what's going on?
Where am I?
You might know what I've been.
I just give you a little bit more
dimensional juice or whatever.
You never did come
with a chill name for that.
I remember my straws.
The city power line of
my microglitter version.
I could generate a little more
concentrated dark energy.
Shoot.
What I love about science.
I'd definitely enough to get me
somewhere with a full size collider.
and Spider-Man.
I'll make you pay.
Everything you took away from me.
All right, this is gonna work.
Or vaporize me and everything in
this building, which would not be good.
Shoot.
What?
There you come.
Replay complete.
Oh, I'm right, right, right, right.
What?
What, what, what, what, what?
Hi.
What you doing?
Nothing.
Uh, good.
All good.
Yeah, everything's good.
Um, bye.
Where's the, the bad guy
you were supposed to monitor?
You just stepped out for a moment.
Dude.
Look, he's just some villain of the week.
I'm a, oh, we don't need tracking.
Oh, hey, look, I got him.
Nope.
They're mine.
Hold on.
Ah, slippery day.
Did you go see your little fart?
What?
No.
Miles?
I mean, are you kidding me right now?
Briefly.
From afar.
How far?
Like, you know, about this?
Uh, that's way too close.
Girl.
I just, look, I had to know how he was.
I, I honestly can't with you.
I know I messed up, okay?
He can't be part of this.
I know.
I'll never see him again.
All right?
No kidding!
Hey, guys.
Guys, he's making his own portals.
What?
He can jump wherever he wants.
He could be a total cannon killer.
You said he was the villain of the week.
Do you know how bad this is for you?
Every dimension he
stops at has an alchemist.
What's he up to?
I don't know.
He's making himself more
powerful so he can beat me.
No.
Amazing.
My star pupil, everyone.
I'll get him, OK?
I can get back up.
If Miguel finds out I'd like you to come.
Don't tell Miguel.
He'll kick me out of him.
What if he sends me home?
I got him.
Earth, 51-01.
What do you want to do?
You never made a mistake.
Never got too close to someone.
I did.
But I got over it.
Alert the local spider.
Tell him when we'll meet him.
I'm on it.
Well, thank you.
Thank you so much for coming here.
You're welcome.
You got an hour to fix this.
I can't help you.
What about us?
I have eyes on the anomaly.
Try getting hands up.
Stop covering.
You're literally hovering.
Hello, pardon me, locals.
Wow, four on there.
Wow.
That's very dangerous.
That looks good.
Which way to out the man?
Who?
It's a place for the big collider.
Hey, Kelsey.
Move over.
That's the best you can do.
Whoa.
I'm here to help.
Mom?
No.
Oh, neither was I. I'm in the zone.
I got you.
Did you follow?
No.
I just saw where you went and
went there without you knowing.
You're not supposed to be here.
What are you talking about?
I'm out with you.
I shouldn't have ever come to see you.
Hey Puff, he's Miles and he wasn't invited.
Oh, you weren't invited
and you came anyway.
Right.
Hey, you guys must be in love with you.
Okay.
No, I'm not.
Oh, I'm very good at reading this.
Who are you?
I'm glad you lost you guys.
I'm not a new guy.
My name is Perfectra Kropaka
and for the past six months.
And even he got a walk?
Yeah.
The Spider-Man is so easy.
I wake up, skip the walk
out because I'm naturally
buff and I don't want to
get too big, you know?
Do almost nothing with my amazing head.
You don't use any product at all.
Just coconut oil, prayer, some genetics.
I sleep by school, don't really
have to try but I do anyway.
Fight a few bad guys,
feed a few street dogs,
quick break for a couple
of chai with my my auntie.
I love chai tea.
What did you just say?
Shai tea chai means tea bro.
You're saying tea tea.
Would I ask you for a coffee
coffee with room for cream cream?
I'm so sorry.
Then, I hang out with
my girlfriend, Guy, I think.
She's an extremely classy teenager.
Hey girl, tonight I was thinking.
Hello, police inspector, saying this
is your daughter, I do not know both.
And, stop it off, I live in the best possible
Spider-Man city, come back, quick talk.
This is where the traffic is, which is where the traffic is, which is where the traffic is, which is where the traffic
is, which is where the traffic is, which is where the traffic is, which is where the traffic is, which is where
the traffic is, which is where the traffic is, which is where the traffic is, which is where the traffic is, which
is where the traffic is, which is where the traffic is, which is where the traffic is, which is where the traffic is.
Oh, Spider-Man.
Hi.
Hey.
Not you.
Are you talking to him or me or me?
That's me.
I think he means me.
Yeah.
Him.
I got this, guys.
Huh?
Wow.
How are you?
I'm on a journey of self-improvement.
And you came to India.
That's the rest of you.
Don't eat free, love me, bro.
No, no, no, no, no.
I didn't mean to like that.
No, let me guess.
You want to ask me about
Satron and Cardamom?
No, I'm ready.
It's the same.
Chai-d. Oh, I love Chai-ti.
No!
Stop about this, fine.
You made me feel empty,
like I had a hole inside of me.
Y'all had holes.
But now I found out what
to fill that hole up with.
More holes.
Said this doesn't make any sense.
It will.
Okay, I'm good.
Don't worry.
We will.
This romantic tension is so palpable.
If Spock gets more holes, you
know they won't be unstoppable.
We can't let him get to out tonight.
See?
How can you guys even concentrate?
Hey, does he move out of me?
What should I know about Hobie?
Oh, looks like he did not know.
Oh, I feel it, like so.
Why are you pleased he had to
make this wonderfully strong bad?
You can't be turned off into the glider
sequences to bring colliders equals.
I'm going to be so much
more than a villain of the week.
I'm sorry.
I called you that, OK?
You're a great villain.
Well, I get enough.
I visualize it, collider.
How's it going now?
Great.
Anyone got any ideas?
Oh, I have so many but none for this.
Stand back.
I've been working on something new.
I love this is usually dangerous.
Give me a second week.
Do you want us to do something?
Or do we just stand here?
Are you like charging it?
Oh, I'm absorbing it, so I can shoot it.
It looks like you're just following me.
Please, open questions.
Oh, it's just breaking the table.
I don't need to do this.
I love how many different
variations of you guys are out there.
What's this dude saying?
It's English for, we got along
great and gross, gross friends.
Is this thing under from 1610?
You understand?
He'll be.
Thanks for breaking the shield.
I loosened it.
They're the best.
Use the palm, but just your finger.
I'll stop you soon.
Is he breathing from his armpits?
Miles, hope you heard me last.
Hi, I've never heard of you because
Ben barely ever mentioned you.
Hi, my name's Obu, Obu, Brian.
I was bitten by.
What did you like to know?
Yeah, man.
For the last three years, I've been the one and only wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
I thought you hated ladies.
Wendy, you left a jumper around my place.
Well, what's his jump?
It's a sweater.
How many sweaters do you have?
Uh, that's, that's not my name.
Sure.
I need to eat brush.
Wait, what?
Well, there's my chucks.
Don't make a heck of a tumor.
I don't mean a theme.
Would you, in a man?
I don't believe he consistently.
This guy is killing you.
This is gonna be good for a spider now.
You and me were finally
going to live up to a potential.
You'll finally have a
villain worth fighting.
And I will be just a joke to you!
You're not a joke, right, Gabe?
Absolutely not a new thing!
I don't believe it's over there!
Just kidding!
See?
No one here thinks you're a joke!
You won't have to miss.
No!
Well, that was another easy
adventure for Spiderman!
Our future.
I'm going to take everything from you.
What?
See you back home.
We'll clear the path.
You slow down that build.
I'll do it, but not because you know we do.
hands up.
Markers are predicting an incoming
cannon event such very carefully.
You don't need to bring the bell, right?
It's two games.
I'll be okay.
I'm wrong.
I was so worried.
You seem like a nice young
woman that I do not know.
Not bad, right?
Right.
I've never seen him so emotional.
Excellent job.
Man, rock, miles, my God!
So, what do you think?
What I always think?
You're amazing.
You make a good team.
Yeah?
Yeah.
What's that?
It's a metaphor for happiness.
It's a lot worse than that.
Hey guys, secure the area, clear all
civilians and let's contain this quantum hole.
Hey, I'm Miles.
We actually met before
when I was in the visible.
I know.
Is everything going to be okay?
Let me, let me in.
Miguel, once you back at HQ.
Miles was just about to head out.
All of you.
I don't follow orders.
Leave it as he.
I'm invited to HQ.
Woo!
How will you even cool her under your mask?
Oh, there's cool the whole time.
Over here.
This place is wild!
Can you sign us by?
Let me else!
Hey!
Anybody's fox talk?
Oh, so, find anybody else back though?
No, you mentioned it.
Oh, you know.
We need to run us.
This is unbelievable.
This is the lobby.
Oh, they're called spiders inside of these.
What happened to that
small elite strike team?
A lot of these are per time.
Wendy, how much have you told him?
About his place and all this.
A little.
Maybe not enough.
Here.
Oh, my own watch!
It's a day pass.
This just keeps you from doing that.
The big one.
The Peter.
Hey, I'm out.
Hey, Peter.
I'm a new recruit.
Peter, take a team to the transport
deck to help deal with this spot mess.
I'm going to call it a mess.
More like a success in progress.
Ben, I need you.
Sorry.
I can't talk right now.
I'm thinking about my past.
Actually, we need you here for some reason.
That was a particularly harrowing memory.
Does he open up?
Oh, names website.
What?
Is the force need a
mess to conceal her face?
Who is in these laser cage?
Anomalies.
Folks who wound up in the wrong convention.
You kicked their butt since then I'm home.
They're not where you're just doing.
What?
We got a bunch of dogs.
That's interesting.
A Mysterio.
Mm-hmm.
Wow.
Video game guy.
I love video games.
Another video game guy.
Are you starting to mean?
Type, face.
Go to Hell, Pentecost, Spider-Man.
Boom.
An interesting craving, a boring rhino.
A Crowler?
Crowler?
Not your proler.
Hey.
True to Stan.
Code, I want myself.
I slipped.
You what?
OK, I did all the work.
I'm ambitious.
Have you been on together?
Oh, not that many.
Not who doesn't.
That's cool.
Sorry.
Oh, no way.
All of us are.
Can we just keep moving forward?
What are you?
I'm an avatar.
My body's back to my parents to mention
cheer when we thank you and anything else.
Here is better.
Hear that.
What is that?
Apart from having a great name?
Go home, Missy.
What'd I say?
I voted against him.
He was attacked with every
command community in the internet.
Insanity there.
Super humane and not creepy.
We should go.
We don't want to close.
Let's see her, huh?
Let's go!
Hey, good luck out there, man.
Okay, bye!
Miguel's out there, great.
He likes those empanadas
from the cafeteria.
Don't ask them why.
My name is Miguel O'Hara.
And this dimension is
one and only Spider-Man.
At least I was.
But I'm not like the image.
I don't always like what I have to do,
but I know I have to be the one to do it.
I've given up too much to stop now.
Oh, no.
Bet this doesn't even do anything.
Maybe you did before
you ripped it out of a walk.
Let's put that in the bro to
distract you from the truth.
And what's that?
I ain't got Scooby-Doo, mate,
because that's what I want.
Why do you want to be part of this law?
Say, get a watch.
You're a watch.
But you've got a nice set up, man.
Nice parents.
They're fine.
We got a fight.
They just want what's best for me.
Nice bloody shame.
Why?
Because you're not
ready for everybody else.
Listen to me, Bob.
Hope you'll be inspired to
manage your independence.
Being your own boss, you'll need all this.
Why are you here?
Look her out from my drummers, huh?
I want to be in a band.
I want to see my friends,
and I need a watch to do that.
Guys, come on.
All right.
Squashed.
Just don't unless you
know what will you find.
Yeah, I know it's long.
But it's his thing.
Miguel O'Hara?
Meet Miles Morales.
Hey, get down, deal.
Ask me, Spanish.
I'm really excited to get going.
I'm the first new ideas
on how to cast the spot.
Oh, wow.
I'm so excited.
He's worried about Spot.
I'll worry about Spot.
What did I do?
Miguel, it's not his fault.
You blew another hole in the multiverse.
He doesn't know any better.
I do know what, uh, not know
what you did when... and you...
I was gonna try to ignore you.
I just can't.
Right, even here.
Or yet.
What's happening?
Hey, Miguel!
Come on, go easy on the kid.
He had a terrible teacher.
He had no chance.
Peter.
Oh boy, unbelievable reality
Spider-Man has arrived.
Oh, dude.
Don't be afraid of my friend Miguel.
He just looks scary.
He's got nobody.
You're growing up on me, look great.
You look... You look solid, you know?
Define solid.
What happened?
You bleeding from the armpits?
Peter, you don't worry about the suit.
We'll get you a new suit.
Peter, you gotta tell him, wave.
What is that?
Matey!
You have a baby?
I have a baby.
This is crazy.
Don't forget to keep your
little day pass on, honey.
I do have one too.
I didn't know they made those for adults.
Give me a second.
Matey!
Kids are not okay.
Come on, honey.
Come on.
Here I go.
I knew I was going to regret
making her that web shooter.
I shouldn't have done it.
That's an actual mistake.
Hey, you want to see pictures?
She's right there.
So it's big.
She's incredible.
Yep.
This is her funny thing.
That's her math face.
This one is the studious one.
Watch out.
The next one you're going to crack up.
You're going to crack up.
Oh, look, I was going to die.
I'm trying to all the
serious about conversation.
You know, you're the only
Spider-Man who isn't funny.
We're supposed to be funny.
The fate of the multiverse.
You always lose me with that.
You say the fate of the
multiverse and my brain dies.
We are.
You guys smell that?
Mayday took a crap.
She's a partner.
Miles.
He disrupted a can in event.
The kid wasn't thinking.
That's not how he works.
That's insulting.
Taking a crap on the
establishment, I salute you.
Wait, what are you upset about?
I saved those people.
And that's the problem.
Lila, do the thing.
Huh?
What thing?
What do you mean, what thing?
The information explain anything.
OK.
What's this?
This is everything.
Can you be more specific?
Can you not talk for a second?
This year, this is all of us.
All of our lives woven together in
a beautiful web of life and destiny.
The spider verse.
Spider verse.
Oh, that's stupid.
It's called the arachnocumoid poly
multiverse, which sounds stupid too, I guess.
And these notes were the lines converge?
They are the canon.
Chapters that are a part of
every spider story, every time.
Some good, some bad.
Some very bad, really.
This cute goal.
Uncle Aaron.
This one, event ASM 90.
A police captain close to
Spiderman dies, saving a kid
from falling rubble during a
battle with an arch nemesis.
Captain Stacy.
I'm so sorry.
That happened to you.
And with me.
Hey, what of it?
That's how the story's supposed to go.
Canon events are the connections
that bind our lives together.
But those connections can be broken.
That's why anomalies are so dangerous.
Inspector Singh's death was a canon event.
You weren't supposed to be there,
and you weren't supposed to save them.
That's why Gwen tried to stop you.
I thought you were trying to save me.
I was.
I was doing both.
And now, Miles, because you changed the
story, Pervitra's dimension is unraveling.
If we're lucky, we can stop it.
We haven't always been lucky.
That wasn't me.
That was the spot.
It's what happens when
you break the cannon.
How do you know?
Because I broke it once myself.
I found a world where I had
a family, where I was happy.
At least a version of me was.
And that version of myself was killed.
So I replaced him.
I thought it was harmless.
But I was wrong.
Isn't that right, Peter?
Yeah.
You break enough can
and save enough captains.
And we could lose everything.
My dad is about to be character.
I'm gonna dig everything from you.
Like you took everything from me.
Spot doesn't.
He kills him.
When does it happen?
In two days.
When he's sworn in.
That's what the model says.
I'm sorry, Miles.
Simmy home.
I can't do that.
What am I supposed to do?
Just let him die.
What about your dad?
He's a captain, right?
Yeah.
And that's it.
You just aren't gonna do anything about it.
Okay, what about Uncle Ben?
That have been okay if you
knew and you just let it play out?
Not for Uncle Ben.
Most of us wouldn't be here, Miles.
And all the good we did it,
it wouldn't have been done.
So we're just supposed
to let people die because
some algorithm says that
that's supposed to happen.
You realize how messed
up that sounds, right?
You have a choice between saving one person
and saving an entire world, every world.
I can do both!
Spider-Man, always, always.
Miles, we all want to live
the life we wish we had.
Believe me, I have tried.
And the harder I tried,
the more damage I did.
You can't have it all, kid.
Being Spider-Man is a sacrifice.
That's the job.
That's what you signed up for.
My hands.
Eddie?
What is this?
Is this an intervention or something?
We know it's hard.
But it's the truth, Miles.
Is that why you hear me?
So let me down easy.
Last time, why not run it back, huh?
Hey, hold on, hold on, right, Quinn.
You should have never come to see you.
Kids, stop calling me.
There we go.
Help me in the hell.
Thank you.
Good.
Miles, please understand,
ask me not to save my father.
I'm not asking.
I'm not just giving you a service.
Great love.
We let him leave, but only
do more damage, both of you.
Go, go, go, go.
Just need to hold you a few days.
It's only been the end like this kid.
Nice edge.
Time to call me that.
All right.
So I'm for doing this.
This is bad parenting.
Just for the rest of that quiz.
Hehe.
Let me guess, he died.
I'm a huge fan of your work.
Do you spite her people to
often use comedy at the press?
Get it, press.
I can do anything he can.
Oh, dang, I've got something.
There's nowhere to run.
My bad, everybody.
There was nowhere to run.
I've got you trapped in my
well-defined musculature, so don't even...
No, let me go crazy to run
running is the least crazy thing
going on I feel bad good,
but this is just how stuff works.
You're not gonna win here.
I don't know No, do you
want to hold my baby?
What?
We could just give the baby
one squeeze and then we'll
talk because I think it's
gonna change our father.
Oh, very rejuvenating.
I'm plenty juvenile.
You'll get far so when you could
just adjust with this magical time.
You don't need to have a
heartfelt conversation with you.
You're the baby, we'll see what happens.
You're the reason I had her, okay?
I thought that if I did a
decent job raising her, then
there was a chance she
was gonna turn out like you.
And that got me excited because
you are a wonderful person.
And I like being around you.
Why didn't you come see me?
I couldn't.
I wanted to be with you guys so badly.
But this thing isn't what I thought it was.
Look, bad things are gonna happen.
It makes us who we are.
But good things happen too, you know?
Like you happen.
And she happened.
Hey, I don't know.
And you are so bad at holding a baby.
That's your location, Peter.
Wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no.
You do not have my location over.
Send everything.
No, no, no, no.
I didn't know that promise you.
Please, man, let's talk about this.
We did.
Good talk.
Yeah.
I don't think he planned this out.
If I hadn't said it before, by
the way, you're a terrible mentor.
He did just beat you, so
I'm not a terrible mentor.
You're both equally terrible.
Does that settle it?
Stop pretending you
know where you're going.
I have a plan.
That's not good.
Huh?
Where is Claus?
Are you sure you're even Spider-Man?
Are you?
Who do you think you are?
Really?
My name is Miles Morales.
I was bitten by a rating active spider.
I'm pretty sorry you.
Oh, right.
Sure.
What's up, man?
You'll be original anomaly
The spider that gave you your
powers wasn't from your dimension.
It was never supposed to bite you.
There's a world out
there with no spider-man
to protect them
because it bit you instead.
You're not supposed to be Spider-man.
No!
You're mine!
I'm Spider-man!
You're a mistake!
If you hadn't been bit, your
Peter Parker would have lived.
Instead, he died.
Saving you.
You would've stopped the
carider before it ever went off.
Spot wouldn't exist.
And none of this would've happened.
And all this time, I have been
the only one holding it all together.
Look, y'all, go easy on it.
You don't belong here.
You never did.
I don't know if we've talked about this.
Is it what we talked about?
You talked about this?
You know?
You all knew?
I...
I didn't know.
How did he tell you?
That's why you never came to see me.
Miles, it's for your own good.
Hold aside, sir!
I'm not a kid, Gwen.
That's exactly what you are.
You're just a kid.
There's no idea.
What is doing?
My dear little hundreds of spider
people away from your own products.
I guess you've got to plan this out.
And I'm about to do this.
Everyone keeps telling me
how my story is supposed to go.
Now, I'm gonna do my own game.
Bye.
I taught him how to do that, so
I got to be a pretty good mentor.
Pull that off.
I don't know.
Stay in there.
Huh?
Hmm.
You can activate it on a cone.
How does that possible?
It isn't.
Hmm!
Oh, okay!
Stop!
It's not the console's fault.
All he had to do was listen.
What an e-listener.
Maybe you weren't hard enough on him.
When, don't do it.
You let him go.
You didn't catch him, go ahead.
Okay, let's all just take a pair of.
You wanna back me up?
Well, okay, Miguel, as a father of
a daughter and the son of a mother.
Yeah, actually, stop talking.
Okay, duly noted.
Let me just talk to you.
He's my friend.
Yeah, and that's the problem.
Do you know for certain what
happens if he breaks the cannon?
Then you want to find out?
I told you she was a liability.
You're wrong.
Jess, tell him he's wrong.
He's not.
Are you serious right now?
I told you.
You let him get away.
I can't help you.
I'm not coming.
You're right.
What the hell?
We are supposed to be the good guys.
We are.
Jess.
Then come with me.
Somebody catch Spot.
Yeah, sorry.
I gotta get her down for her nap.
Not you.
I've had the right amount of you.
Hey, hun.
That was work.
Peter, did you bring our
baby to another fight?
Did I bring our bit?
No.
Because you asked me not.
So I didn't.
I wouldn't.
You think I'll be any good at this?
You're asking that now?
There's no playbook for raising someone
like her or being someone like you.
You just gotta make the
right adjustments at halftime.
That's a sports metaphor, by the way.
I understand.
I'm sorry.
You're just such a nerd, Denise.
Go ahead.
Hey, have a watch sports.
OK.
You want to go easy on the penguin?
Just, would you just,
you didn't even look at me.
What, what, what, what is that?
I'm looking at you, like you asked.
It looks skinny.
Where have you been?
Just been out murdering all my friends.
Oh, oh, that's fine.
Yeah, okay.
Where are you going?
I don't know.
You're a good cop, Dad.
You know, you put on
that badge because you
know, if you don't,
someone who shouldn't will.
But you have to understand.
This mask is my badge.
And I'm trying to be good too.
I was trying so hard to wear
this thing the way you would want.
And I didn't.
I didn't.
I can do all these things, but I
can't help the people I love the most.
And they can only know half of who I am.
So I'm completely on my own.
And now I don't even know
who the right thing is anymore.
I don't know what I'm
supposed to do, but I know.
I can't lose one more friend.
When do I always talk
you to do it by the book?
Yeah, and how did that work out?
I took an oath.
Then arrest me, dad.
Get it over.
I can't.
Why not?
Because I quit.
When?
About halfway through your big speech.
You're not going to be captain.
That means my job being captain
this whole thing doesn't matter anymore.
You're the best thing I've ever done.
It was a good speed, too.
No one of you got an A in English.
B, I got to be, plus, missed a few classes.
I don't know what it is you got to do.
But I think that this
thing is supposed to help.
The guy who left it
was a real piece of work.
How do you like that?
Promise.
Parenting.
Stuff.
Big ass mystery.
You have to be missed.
You're a Peter Parker with a plan.
And none of this would have happened.
Mom, the hardest thing about this
job is you can always save everybody.
I'll make people with everything.
Between saving one person and
saving an entire world, every world.
Spider-Man, all the way home.
Whatever you're going to do right there,
don't have a lot of sad things are good.
I didn't know how it's helped me.
Did you check your locations?
Yes, Dan.
Simon, my luck.
Would you just say everyone out?
Anywhere.
Anywhere he might be.
I can grab the captain.
You call me Donaldson.
I'm sworn in.
We're all proud of you.
See you there.
There's something unusual happening.
My land?
Is now a bad time?
Am I too late?
You should do the year ahead.
Are you guys okay?
Tell me okay.
I'm okay.
You were right.
You were right about everything.
Plus I'm late.
I saw all these amazing places
and met all these amazing people.
But... Get that boss on me, old...
But they didn't want me.
I kept thinking about what you said.
I let him have it, Mom.
I beat him all.
I know how strong I am now.
I'm strong because of you.
And dad, it's okay, Tom.
And us.
Mom.
There's something coming for us.
Something, something terrible.
Miles, you're talking crazy.
What's going on?
His name is Spock.
He's my nemesis.
And I'm gonna stop him.
I know you know I've been lying to you.
It's because I thought if you knew,
you wouldn't love me the same.
And then I went out there and
now I'm not afraid of any day.
What do you want to tell me?
You've got to promise
nothing's going to change.
But I will always love you.
You've got to promise.
Always.
I don't care what you say.
Don't end this.
I'm Spiderman.
Who's Spider-Man?
The superhero?
He got bit by Spider?
And gave him spider powers?
He's me?
Is this one like a dress up
like your favorite character?
Or, like, what's it called?
Like, comics con.
I don't know what that is.
You really have me going there, Spider-Man.
You might be not there.
What do you have eat arms?
Do you push silk out of your kulito head?
And I'm out there once, but no.
Are you sure you woke up?
Mom, stop playing around.
This is serious.
Dad worked with Spider-Man.
I mean, he didn't realize
Spider-Man was me at the time, but...
This dad was here to explain this.
Miles, please.
I got me to take care of.
So help me now.
Hold on.
I need to talk.
Who's in the wrong universe?
A spider that gave you your powers.
What is from your connection?
42.
You tell him to mention.
I'm so sick.
I have a shame.
Didn't send me off.
Okay.
Oh.
I missed you so much.
Okay.
All right, then.
Whoa, you took your braids out?
Uh, on purpose?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm still getting used to it.
They gave me more hours
of the hustlers the next month.
I swear I was done.
I'm a fan.
Hey, how are you doing?
Hey, how'd it go with Miles?
Well, you know how you grounded him?
Mm-hmm.
I ungrounded him.
You, you what?
A little.
How much shall we begin to take?
A lot of trouble.
I don't think that.
Oh, Miles, I have to
work an overnight tonight.
Here's a grocery list.
I'll make sure he gets he's done.
All right, we got a rope.
Security switches out of
six, that's the window, right?
Right, yeah.
I'm following you in what you are saying.
You all right?
I have a call.
Come over.
Make sure you got the plan.
Yeah, but maybe we should go over it one
more time just to make sure there's no need.
It's nice right in there.
But you did unilaterally unwell.
I just, I just worry about it.
This is probably that girl.
What is he even thinking being with her?
I have some ideas.
Baby, you're really not helping us.
She's so the way you lit up around her.
I just hope she doesn't get in her.
I mean, am I responsible for this?
No, maybe it's all my fault.
Come on, but you're a great dad.
This is hard.
It's hard.
It's like we got our own new kid
who just wants to grow up so fast.
And maybe we got to grow up, too.
A little bit.
Maybe we just got to let
him spread his wings, man.
Man, it's not your fault.
It's mine.
Oh, come on.
What the heck are you doing here?
Oh, his window was open, so I
came in because that's normal to do.
I want to talk to your parents.
Right, Maya.
My dad's kind of hard to get on the horn.
Oh, really?
What does he do?
Deal drugs?
He's a cop.
Statement with drunk.
Yep, well, I'm gonna call the station.
I don't think he's there,
or anywhere around here.
Well, that's his jacket, emo.
Where's Miles?
I don't know.
You don't know?
What do you mean you don't know?
I'll leave.
What do you think you're going on, lady?
I'm going to find him.
I don't know where, exactly.
But I know where to start.
One thing I learned from
Miles, it's all possible.
He loves you more than
you could ever imagine.
I've seen it.
If you do, find him.
Tell him five months.
And tell him we love him.
You got it.
I'm listening.
Okay.
Don't understand.
I'm not from here.
Listen.
Okay.
This machine sits in here around the state.
Wait, please.
Please.
I'll go here.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Please, go Aaron.
Just hear me out.
I was bit by a spider that gave me powers.
Pain wasn't supposed to bite me.
It was supposed to bite someone else.
Something from here.
I have an uncle Aaron too.
I had a lot of bad things.
I knew he wanted to be good.
He just didn't know he
had a choice, but you do.
You be a good guy?
A good guy.
Please, you trust me.
I know you don't want to be the problem.
on that.
Your dad is still alive.
You know what?
Your father.
You said he's still alive.
Yeah.
Who are you?
My mom's my dad lives.
But you, you can call me the problem.
If I don't get home,
our dad is going to die.
You're dead.
Please.
You have to let me go.
Why would I do that?
I never found the right band to join.
So I started my own.
For the few old friends.
When I don't fight, I don't feel
like I don't stand like dreaming.
It's time for my life, cause I'm a feeling.
I get so little too much, I can't be dead.
When I can't kill one, I'm still fighting.
I don't feel I've lost in my dream
It's been more like us coming
in Like it's someone too much
and you'll be there But I can't give
I can't find anything to myself to just walk
away I can't find anything to myself to lose
anything But I know once it gets me, no one need
to be good I can't find what my love will do
just to save you I give all of me yeah I can be screaming now
calling me it's my fault major fault for me so to save you I
give my own just to save you I give all of me I can be screaming
now calling me it's my fault major fault for me so to save you
you fell from me I count on you in times of
truth instead of holding you down I should
I'm pulling strings real Just to save you, I
give all of me Yeah, I can be screaming now
calling me It's my fault made you fall for me
So to save you, I give my all Just to save you
You help me down on a stack of
the bottle, that is like it's really all.
I know they can't stand me.
I know no numbers down your
bros go, I know diamonds dancing.
I bet you up and I really won't say it.
When I'm sorry, I'm just clearing.
I gave you this number, there's
nobody else that got it, you can call me.
The way I let you come into my life and take
my heart over here, it's like a robbery.
Every time you look up on the charts,
now you're saying me, I'll be proud of me.
I got your guts down, patted, police, and
Just to save you, I give you all of me.
I can hear you screaming now calling me.
It's my fault made you fall for free.
So to save you.